Finding Aid for BMC Media Services records, 1851-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Faculty and Staff Portraits
  - D-E
    - DeMuth, George R., 1950; 1957; 1972; undated (Box 2)
    - Dengiz, Alan, Geriatrics, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Dennis, Robert, Gerontology, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Dent, Thomas, Surgery, 1981; 1983 (Box 2)
    - Denton, Samuel, undated (Box 2)
    - Denver, Robert, Reproductive Sciences, 1996 (Box 2)
    - Deshpande, Manjushree, Family Medicine, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Devaney, Eric, Thoracic Surgery, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Devejian, Neil, Thoracic Surgery, 1999; 2000 (Box 2)
    - Devine, (?), Pharmacy, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Deweese, Marion, Vascular Surgery, undated (Box 2)
    - Di Ponio, Lisa, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Diana, Joseph A., 1960; 1967 (Box 2)
    - Dick, Macdonald, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Dickinson, Chris, Pediatric Gastroenterology, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Dickinson, David G., Pediatrics, 1954; 1963; 1972 (Box 2)
    - Dilts, Preston, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1981; 1989; undated (Box 2)
    - Dimaraki, Eleni, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Ding, Qi, Dermatology, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Dingman, Reed O. (includes wife), 1956; 1958; 1960; 1962; 1967; 1982 (Box 2)
    - Diokno, Ananias C., Urology, 1976; 1979; 1981 (Box 2)
    - Dishell, (?), 1995 (Box 2)
    - Distler, Jack J., 1967 (Box 2)
    - Dixon, Jack, Medical Center Development, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Dixson, J. B., 1971 (Box 2)
    - Dlugosz, Anj, Medical Administration, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Doble, J., Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Dock, George, undated (Box 2)
    - Dohm-Parker, Nicole, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 2)
    - Domino, Edward F., Pharmacology, 1964; 1968; 1970; 2001; undated (Box 2)
    - Domino, Steven, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Dorr, Richard, Urology, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Douyon, Liselle, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Downing, Joe, General Surgery, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Downing, Mary, Anesthesiology 1997 see Bradley, Kathryn, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Downs, Katie, Ophthalmology, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Dries, David, Trauma and Burn, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Duboff, Gregory, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1968; 1973; undated (Box 2)
    - Duff, Ivan, Internal Medicine, 1948; 1950; 1951; 1955; 1967; 1983; undated (Box 2)
    - Dunlay, James, Family Practice, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Dunn, Stephen, Pediatrics 2000 also see Faix, Roger, Pediatrics, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Dunnick, N. Reed, Medical Center Development, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Dunster, Edward Swift, undated (Box 2)
    - Durka-Pelok, Geraldine, Medical School Administration, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Durovich, Christopher, Internal Medicine, 1996 (Box 3)
    - Durrant, Valerie, Epidemiology, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Dusina, Debbie, Cardiology, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Dutta, Suparna, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Duwe, Douglas, Pediatrics, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Eagle, Kim, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Easterling, Ronald E., Internal Medicine, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Edmunds, Charles Wallace, undated (Box 3)
    - Edwards, Gloria, Credit Union, undated (Box 3)
    - Edwards, Jonathan, Neurology, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Elger, William, Executive Director for Administration and Chief Financial Officer of the Medical School, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Elkin, Ellen, Microbiology and Immunology, 2000; 2001 (Box 3)
    - Elsholz, Daniel, Endocrinology and Metabolism, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Engleberg, Cary, Internal Medicine, 2001 (Box 3)
    - English, Grace, Neurology, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Ensing, Gregory, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Eppinger, Mike, Thoracic Surgery, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Ernst, Calvin B., Surgery, 1968 (Box 3)
    - Ernst, Susan, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 3)
    - Ernst, Robert, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Escher, Allan, Anesthesiology, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Esfandiari, Nazanene, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Eswara, Pallavi, Human Genetics, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Etemad, Jeff, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Evans, Tommy N., Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1965 (Box 3)
    - Everett, Jeff, Thoracic Surgery, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Everson, Susan, School of Public Health, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Evi-Ju, Son, Neurology, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Eyler, Evan, Medical School Administration, M Works, 1997; 2000 (Box 3)
    - Fader, Darrell, Dermatology, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Faix, Roger, Pediatrics, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Fajans, Stefan S., Internal Medicine, 1948; 1955-1960; 1964; 1985; undated (Box 3)
    - Falls, Harold F., Ophthalmology, 1954; 1966; 1969; undated (Box 3)
    - Fante, Robert, Ophthalmology, undated (Box 3)
    - Fantone, Joseph, Pathology, 1989 (Box 3)
    - Farhat, Saeed M., 1963; 1967; 1973; 1998; undated (Box 3)
    - Farley, Frances, Orthopedic Surgery, undated (Box 3)
    - Fatchett, Deb, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Fayos, Juan V., Radiation Therapy, 1972; 1974 (Box 3)
    - Feagin, Susan, Development and Communications, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Fekety, F. Robert, Jr., Internal Medicine, 1977; 1991; undated (Box 3)
    - Feldman, Eva, Neurology, 1989 (Box 3)
    - Feldstein, (?), undated (Box 3)
    - Feller, Irving, Burn Unit, 1958; 1964; 1968; 1970; undated (Box 3)
    - Fendrick, Mark, Internal Medicine, 1995 (Box 3)
    - Ferguson, (?), undated (Box 3)
    - Finch, (?), 1989 (Box 3)
    - Finch, Stu M., 1967; 1968 (Box 3)
    - Fine, Paul, Internal Medicine, 1992; 2001 (Box 3)
    - Fink, John, Neurology, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Fiore, Tina, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1997 (Box 3)
    - Fish, (?), Radiation Therapy, undated (Box 3)
    - Fishman, Simon, Neurology, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Fitzbutler, William Henry, undated (Box 3)
    - Fitzgerald (?), Internal Medicine, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Fleming, Arthur, undated (Box 3)
    - Fleming, Denise, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Flint, Andrew, Medical School Administration, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Florentino, Renee, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Floyd, John C., Internal Medicine, 1974; 1981 (Box 3)
    - Fluent, Tom, Psychiatry, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Foley, William D., Radiology, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Fontana, Robert, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Ford, William J. A. (?), Radiology, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Forman, Glenn, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1999; undated (Box 3)
    - Foster, (?), Communication Disorders, 1997 (Box 3)
    - Foster, Carol, Pediatrics and Endocrinology, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Foster, Douglas, Obstetrics and Gynecology Reproductive Sciences Program, 1998; undated (Box 3)
    - Foster, Kristen, Reproductive Sciences, 1997 (Box 3)
    - Foster, Norman, Neurology, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Fowlkes, J. Brian, Radiology, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Fox, David, Internal Medicine, 1991; 2000; 2001 (Box 3)
    - Fox, Kenneth, Pediatric Cardiology, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Fox, Sarah, Family Practice, 1983 (Box 3)
    - Fox, Sharon, Thoracic Surgery, 1997 (Box 3)
    - Foyt, Howard, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Fralick, Bruce (includes family), Ophthalmology, 1958; 1968; 1971 (Box 3)
    - undated (Box 3)
    - Francis, Thomas, Jr., 1955; 1957 (Box 3)
    - Francke, Don, undated (Box 3)
    - Frank, Jennifer, Family Practice, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Freed, Gary, Pediatrics, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Freed, Jana, Family Medicine, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Freeman, Curtis, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 3)
    - French, A. James, 1950; 1953; 1955; 1956; 1967 (Box 3)
    - French, Arthur B., Internal Medicine, 1960; 1964; 1967; 1973; undated (Box 3)
    - Frey, Charles F., 1967 (Box 3)
    - Frey, Jamie, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Frey, Kirk, Alumni and Development, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Freymuth, Angela, Psychiatry, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Fritz, Irving B., Physiology (Box 3)
    - Frohlich, Moses M., 1956; undated (Box 3)
    - Frost, Marie, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Fry, (?), undated (Box 3)
    - Fry, William, Surgery, 1954; 1959; 1972; 1974
    - Fu, Eric, General Surgery, 1997 (Box 3)
    - Fu, Zheng, Immunology, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Fuchs, Nomi, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Fuentes, Maren, Microbiology and Immunology, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Fuller, Jenny, Immunology, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Funda, Meric, Surgery, undated (Box 3)
    - Furicchia, (?), Nuclear Medicine, 1996 (Box 3)
    - Furney, Scott, Internal Medicine, 1995 (Box 3)
    - Furstenberg, Albert C., Dean of Medical School, Otolaryngology, 1949; 1958; undated (Box 3)
  - G-I
    - Gabrielson, Trygve O., 1967; 1972; 1974 (Box 3)
    - Gafni, Ari, Alumni and Development, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Gage, Lois, School of Nursing, 1996 (Box 3)
    - Gago, (?), Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1997 (Box 3)
    - Gago, Otto, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Gahagan, Sheila, Pediatrics, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Garfield, Robert L., Administrative Assistant, 1960; 1962 (Box 3)
    - Garner, Warren, Surgery, Trauma Burn Unit, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Garr, Warren, Family Practice, 1979 (Box 3)
    - Garrick, Jim, Pharmacy, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Garvin, Ann, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 3)
    - Gatza, Erin, Immunology, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Gaucher, (?), 1997 (Box 3)
    - Gaucher, Internal Medicine, 1983 (Box 3)
    - Gauger, Paul, Surgery, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Gay, Steven, Pulmonology, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Gay, Tamara, Psychiatry, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Gelb, Doug, Neurology, 1999 (Box 3)
    - George, Conrad, undated (Box 3)
    - Gerhardt, Phillip, Bacteriology, undated (Box 3)
    - Germiller, John, Alumni and Development, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Geronimus, Arline, Public Health, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Geyer-Sylvia, Zelda, Medical School Administration, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Gilchrist, Brian, Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Gildorf, Janet, Pediatrics, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Gillespie, Elena, Cardiac Surgery, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Gillum, Linda, Office of Student Programs, 1997 (Box 3)
    - Gilman, Sid, Neurology, 1978; 1979; 1999; undated (Box 3)
    - Gilsdorf, Janet, Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 2000; 2001 (Box 3)
    - Ginsburg, David, Internal Medicine, 2000; 2001 (Box 3)
    - Giordano, Thomas, Alumni and Development, Pathology, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Giordino, Agostino, Internal Medicine, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Gitt, Steven, Plastic Surgery, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Glick, Gary, Chemistry, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Glosser, Jeff, Dental Surgery, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Glover, Roy A., Anatomy, 1982; 2001; undated (Box 3)
    - Godfrey, John, Rackham Graduate School, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Goldberg, Caren, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Goldberg, Edward, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995; 1994; undated (Box 3)
    - Goldman, Edward, Health Systems Attorney, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Goldstein, Irwin, Alumni Development, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Goldstein, Steve, Medical Center Development, 1997 (Box 3)
    - Gomez, Carlen, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Gong, Molly, School of Public Health, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Gordon, David, Pathology, undated (Box 3)
    - Gorelick, Judy, Neurosurgery, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Gorenflo, Dan, Family Medicine, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Gorlich, Adam, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Gorowski, (?), Radiology, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Gosling, John, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1962; 1965; 1968; undated (Box 3)
    - Gotz, Alexander, Medical Center Development, 1996 (Box 3)
    - Goulet, James, Orthopedic Surgery, 1996 (Box 3)
    - Grabb, William, 1952; 1957; 1960; 1961 (Box 3)
    - Gracia, Anne, School of Nursing, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Grady, (?), 1989 (Box 3)
    - Graff, Louis, 1970 (Box 3)
    - Graham, (?), 1978 (Box 3)
    - Graham, Linda, Surgery, undated (Box 3)
    - Graham, Lindsey, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Gratiot-Deans, Jeanne, Nephrology, undated (Box 3)
    - Gray, Barbara, Services for Students with Disabilities, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Gray, Laman A., Thoracic Surgery, Jr., 1974 (Box 3)
    - Grazewski, Lynn, Planning and Marketing, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Graziano, Joseph, Cardiology, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Greden, John, Psychiatry, 1999; undated (Box 3)
    - Green, (?), Allergy, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Green, (?), Endocrinology, 1986; 1992 (Box 3)
    - Green, Robert A., 1972; 1976; 1989 (Box 3)
    - Greene, Douglas, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Greenfield, Jonathan, Pediatric Surgery, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Greenfield, L. John, Neurology, undated (Box 3)
    - Greenfield, Lazar J., Surgery, undated (Box 3)
    - Grekin, Roger J., Internal Medicine, Endocrinology, 1999; 2000 (Box 3)
    - Griesen, James V., 1976 (Box 3)
    - Griffith, (?), Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1997 (Box 3)
    - Griffith, Brian, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Grill, Norma, Planning and Marketing, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Groder, (?), Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 3)
    - Gronbach, Keith, Oral Surgery, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Gronvall, John A., 1972; 1978-1982 (Box 3)
    - Gross, Barry, Alumni and Development, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Grossman, H. Barton, Urology, undated (Box 3)
    - Grossman, Herbert, Pediatric Neurology, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Gruber, Stephan, Medical School Administration, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Grum, Cyril, Internal Medicine, 1989; 2000 (Box 3)
    - Gruppen, Larry, Medical Center Development, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Gunn, Moses, undated (Box 3)
    - Gurule (?), Social Work, 1997 (Box 3)
    - Gyetko, Margaret, Internal Medicine, 1997; 2000 (Box 3)
    - Haar, Floyd, Neurosurgery, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Haas, Felix, Pediatric Cardiology, 1999 (Box 3)
    - Hackley, (?), Communication Disorders, 1997 (Box 3)
    - Hackney, Barbara, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 3)
    - Haefner, Hope, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Haftel, Hilary, Pediatrics, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Hagerty, Bonnie, Nursing, 1995 (Box 3)
    - Haight, Cameron, 1949; 1953; 1955-1957; undated (Box 4)
    - Hak, David, Orthopedic Surgery, undated (Box 4)
    - Hakan, Oral, Cardiology, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Halman, Marc, Radiation Oncology, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Halter, Jeffrey, Internal Medicine, Medical School Administration, 2000; 2001 (Box 4)
    - Hammer, Gary, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Hammond, (?), Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1996 (Box 4)
    - Hammoud, Maya, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Hamouda, Tarek, Alumni and Development, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Han, Jing, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Hanash, Samir, Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 1997; 2001 (Box 4)
    - Hansen, Matthew, Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Harlan, William, 1975; 1978 (Box 4)
    - Harness, Jay K., Surgery, 1979; 1980 (Box 4)
    - Harper, Judith, Financial Aid, 1995 (Box 4)
    - Harrell, E., Richard, Jr., Dermatology, 1960; 1989; undated (Box 4)
    - Harrigan, Mark, Neurosurgery, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Harrison, (?), 1962 (Box 4)
    - Hatcher, Robert L. Hatcher, Communicative Disorders, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Hatfield, Rudolph, Psychiatry, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Hawkins, Joseph, Otolaryngology, undated (Box 4)
    - Hawn, Mary, General Surgery, 1998 (Box 4)
    - Hayes, Daniel, Internal Medicine, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Haynes, Harley A., undated (Box 4)
    - Hayward, Rodney, Internal Medicine, 1994 (Box 4)
    - Headington, John T., 1959; 1972 (Box 4)
    - Heard, Tripp, Nuclear Medicine Fellow, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Heaton, (?), 1989 (Box 4)
    - Hebdon, G. Matthew, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Heidibrink, Judy, Neurology, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Hemilla, Mark, Surgery, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Henderson, John W., Ophthalmology, 1969; 1971; 1975 (Box 4)
    - Henderson, Reuben, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Hendricks, Nancy, Human Resources and Affirmative Action, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Hendrix, Robert C., 1953; 1972 (Box 4)
    - Hendrixson, (?), undated (Box 4)
    - Henke, Peter, Vascular Surgery, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Henley, Keith S., Internal Medicine, 1955; 1957; 1971; 1976; undated (Box 4)
    - Henn, Julia, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Henninger, Nathan, Psychology, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Henry, Jonathan, Family Practice, undated (Box 4)
    - Henry, Rebecca, Microbiology and Immunology, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Hensinger, Robert N., 1976 (Box 4)
    - Hepner, (?), Sports Medicine, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Herdman, William J., undated (Box 4)
    - Herman, (?), 1972; 1976 (Box 4)
    - Herman, William, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Hermann, David, Neurology, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Herwig, (?), undated (Box 4)
    - Hess, George, 1955 (Box 4)
    - Heun, Gisela, Physiology, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Hickenbottom, Susan "Suzy", Neurology, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Hickey, Preston M., Radiology, undated (Box 4)
    - Hicks, Samuel P., 1972 (Box 4)
    - Hidalgo, Eduardo J., Internal Medicine, 1973 (Box 4)
    - Higashi, Tatsuya, Nuclear Medicine, undated (Box 4)
    - Higgins, (?), undated (Box 4)
    - Higuchi, Tetsuya, Nuclear Medicine, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Hildebrandt, H. Mark, Pediatrics, 1968 (Box 4)
    - Hillebrand, Herbert W., Hospital Chaplain, 1972; 1973 (Box 4)
    - Hillemeier, Craig, Pediatrics, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Hilton, James, Center for Research on Learning and Teaching, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Himle, Joseph, Psychiatry, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Hinckley, Jacqueline "Jackie", undated (Box 4)
    - Hinds, Heather, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Hinds, Richard J., 1953 (Box 4)
    - Hinerman, Doun, circa 1958 (Box 4)
    - Hirth, Joann, Surgery, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Hiss, Roland, Medical Center Development, 1963; 1999; undated (Box 4)
    - Ho, Alice, Planning and Marketing, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Hodges, Fred J., 1948-1950; 1954; 1956-1961; 1968; undated (Box 4)
    - Hodges, G.F.G. (Gerald?), undated (Box 4)
    - Hoff, Julian T., 1984; undated (Box 4)
    - Hoffman, Lyn, Medical School Administration, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Holland, Katie, Neurology, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Holmes, Ronald, Pediatrics, 1975 (Box 4)
    - Holt, John F., Radiology, 1949; 1956; 1963; 1969; undated (Box 4)
    - Holzman, Lawrence, Nephrology, Internal Medicine, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Hong, Eunice J., Pharmacology, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Hoobler, Sibley W., Internal Medicine, 1949; 1956; 1964; 1968; undated (Box 4)
    - Hopwood, Nancy, Pediatrics, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Horan, Dennis, Surgery, 1978; 1979 (Box 4)
    - Horman, (?) 1997 also see Miller, (?) Communicative Disorders, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Horton, Kim, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Horton, Muriel, Supervising Nurse in Operating Room, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Hoskins, Phillip A., Radiology, 1964 (Box 4)
    - Hotrey, Rachel, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Housner, Jeffrey, Sports Medicine, 1998; 1999 (Box 4)
    - Howard, Denise, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Howatt, William, Pediatrics, 1960; 1962; 1974; 1990 (Box 4)
    - Howe, Arlene, Hospital Administration, 1962; 1970 (Box 4)
    - Howell, Joel, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Howell, William H., undated (Box 4)
    - Huang, Grace, Psychiatry, 1996 (Box 4)
    - Huang, (?), undated (Box 4)
    - Huban, Tim, Neurology, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Hubbard, William N. Jr., Dean of Medical School, 1960; 1967; 1969; 1970 (Box 4)
    - Huber, G. Carl, Anatomy, undated (Box 4)
    - Hudson, Jill, Human Resources Development, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Huelke, Donald, Anatomy, 1984 (Box 4)
    - Hughes, Bret, Physiology, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Hulin, Marc, Unit for Laboratory and Animal Medicine, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Hultquist, Donald E., 1976 (Box 4)
    - Humes, H. David, Internal Medicine, 1995; 1997; undated (Box 4)
    - Hunsche, Elizabeth, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Hunt, Allen, Bioengineering, Gerontology, 1998 (Box 4)
    - Hunt, Karen, Radiology, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Hunt, Nancy, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 4)
    - Hunt, Tracy, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Hupy, Tom, Family Practice, 1985 (Box 4)
    - Hurd, William W., Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1994 (Box 4)
    - Hutchins, Harry H., undated (Box 4)
    - Hutchinson, Ray, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Hynes, Michelle, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 1999 (Box 4)
  - I-L
    - Ichikawa, Hajime, Pediatric Cardiology, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Ichimaru, Toru, Reproductive Sciences (Box 4)
    - Ignelzi, Michael, Pediatric Dentistry, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Ilaq, Liza, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Imperiale, Mike, Microbiology and Immunology, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Iniguez-Lluhi, Jorge, Pharmacology, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Isaacs, (?), undated (Box 4)
    - Jackson, Cori, Neurology, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Jackson, Leslie, Reproductive Sciences Program, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Jacobi, Kathryn, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Jacobson, Jon, Radiology, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Jacobson, Peter, School of Public Health, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Jaffe, Craig, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Jaffe, Robert B., Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1966 (Box 4)
    - Jakubiak, Ronald J., Neurology, 1973 (Box 4)
    - Jakubzick, Claudia, Immunology, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Jamerson, Kenneth, Hypertension, Internal Medicine, 1998; 2001 (Box 4)
    - Jamieson, Sarah, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Jancik, Amy, Psychology, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Jebson, Peter, Surgery, undated (Box 4)
    - Jechura, Tammy, Psychology, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Jeffries, Frank W., 1962 (Box 4)
    - Jian, Kaza, Medical School Administration (Box 4)
    - Jiang, Yajun, Neurosurgery, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Jibson, Michael, Psychiatry, 1996; 2000 (Box 4)
    - Johns, Nathaniel, Psychiatry, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Johnson, (?), 1961 (Box 4)
    - Johnson, (?), undated (Box 4)
    - Johnson, Ben, undated (Box 4)
    - Johnson, Charles B., Internal Medicine, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Johnson, Joseph, Dean of Medical School, Internal Medicine, 1990; undated (Box 4)
    - Johnson, Karen, Human Genetics, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Johnson, Kathryn, Microbiology and Immunology, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Johnson, Robert D., 1957; 1960; undated (Box 4)
    - Johnson, Steven D., Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 4)
    - Johnson, Timothy M., Dermatology, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Johnson, Timothy R. B., Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995 (Box 4)
    - Johnson, Tom, undated (Box 4)
    - Johnston, Carolyn M., Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 4)
    - Johnston, Franklin D., 1960; 1966; undated (Box 4)
    - Johnston, J. R., 1950 (Box 4)
    - Jokelainen, Pentti, Medical Center Development, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Jones, Beverly, Nursing, 1992 (Box 4)
    - Jones, Dorothy, Pharmacology, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Jones, Lamont, Otolaryngology, Medical School Administration, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Jones, Robert see Thomas, Hugh Owen copy, 1885 (Box 4)
    - Jones, Sophia B., Student, Class of, 1883; undated (Box 4)
    - Jourdian, George W., 1973 (Box 4)
    - Joynt, Robert L., Physical Medicine, 1969 (Box 4)
    - Judge, Richard D., Heart Station, 1952; 1964; 1968; undated (Box 4)
    - Juhasz, Tibor, Ophthalmology, 1998 (Box 4)
    - Julius, Steve, Hypertension, Internal Medicine, 1966; 1990 (Box 4)
    - Junck, Larry, Neurology, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Kagisaki, Koji, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 4)
    - Kahn, Donald, Thoracic Surgery, 1960; 1969; undated (Box 4)
    - Kahn, Edgar, Neurosurgery, 1951; 1953; 1958 (Box 4)
    - Kahn, Reuben L. (includes wife), Serology, Epidemiology, 1949; 1951; 1954; 1956; 1957; undated (Box 4)
    - Kahn, Stephen P., Surgery, 1969 (Box 4)
    - Kales, Helen, Psychiatry, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Kaminski, Mark, Internal Medicine, 1994 (Box 4)
    - Kandala, Geeta, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Kane-Low, Lisa, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 4)
    - Kane-Smart, Sara, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Kang, Sewon, Dermatology, Alumni and Development, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Kao, John, Internal Medicine, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Karby, Melissa, Biostatistics, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Karsh, Fred, Medical School Administration, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Karunakar, Madhar, Orthopedics, 2000 (Box 4)